[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Anything massively surprising there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "JJ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "No, really not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "That she had a massive heart attack of some sort and then drowned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Is the guy that shot this young boy going to get arrested?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, we don't know if he'll get arrested or when he'll get arrested.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "I'm doing well, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I'm going to come back to the campaign in just a moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, my view is that the local district attorney is doing exactly the right thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "And secondly, at what point politically does it become damaging to you to continue to stay in the race if the current rate of delegate gains and state wins by Mitt Romney continues at the pace that it's now happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Well, there are three answers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kennedy Center Honors"], "PERSON": ["Callista"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Newt Gingrich, how do you respond to the charge from one of Hollywood's great actors that you are a hypocrite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, first of all, no matter what words go back and forth between us, Callista and I were delighted to be at the Kennedy Center Honors when he was honored.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hollywood"], "PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Did you really feel offended by Robert De Niro or was it just a chance to whack a Democrat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I really think the use of racism by Democrats is just as bad as the use of racism by Republicans, and I really think it's wrong to use racial references like that, period.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert De Niro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 243, "question": "That the kind of vicious, nasty things he said are OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "ORGAN: No, I actually -- I actually think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Maher"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "-- vicious, nasty things in the left?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "No, but it's interesting you mention Bill Maher because he wrote a very good piece in \"The New York Times\" today precisely about America's collective sense of humor failure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Because everyone is saying that to him about you, but the same applies to you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Well, it applies both ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Are they going to tell Sanchez, move over, because now we have to give Tebow and the wildcat formation time to practice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanchez", "Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "He is not Broadway Joe, is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, I tell you, the way the Jets have played recently, they need the Good Lord on their side.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Broadway Joe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "So you don't think it will be too much temptation for him coming to a city like New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Oh, hey, this young man, I've had had the pleasure of watching him work since he started college in Florida.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "I mean isn't that part of the game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Well, it's part of the game when you don't intentionally want to maim someone, when you don't intentionally say, we need to knock this guy out and you're going to get a bonus if he's carried off the field or you're going to get a different bonus if he has to leave the game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":"], "qSentId": 420, "question": "How long have you two been married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Twenty --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Seven?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "And you're still holding hands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Is this because you're nervous or you still love each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "No, no, no, we're all right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Was it true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I mean I can't imagine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Who's going to be your co-host?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Yes, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mark Sanchez"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Are you excited about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I feel so bad for Mark Sanchez.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "This is not good news, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Well, I tell you, I think -- I used to do sports years ago and I love sports.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrea Mitchell"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "And I'm sure that, you know, if you were still doing the news broadcast and you feel the same way I do, which is, this whole thing of \"Stand Your Ground,\" allowing someone to just apparently follow after this unarmed kid and kill him and not even be arrested in America today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Well, you know, I saw Andrea Mitchell on that other cable station.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Yes, but to me, what bothers me more is, how does the Florida Supreme Court allow that law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "JJR", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Unbelievable.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Florida Supreme Court"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "But I just think it's crazy, crazy, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "And you got the scoop?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nixon"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Isn't that strange?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "That was President Nixon for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan", "Ronald Reagan"]}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "It's vicious, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "It's -- I mean, I really believe -- I mean, Reagan -- Ronald Reagan believed in the 11th amendment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Will you come back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]